<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tony Kappen</title>
    <link>https://tonykappen.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tony Kappen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>© 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 16:33:47 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tonykappen.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo album sharing web application</title>
      <link>https://tonykappen.com/projects/image-collecter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 16:33:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tonykappen.com/projects/image-collecter/</guid>
      <description>A web app written in Golang allows an authenticated user to group their photos into albums and share these albums with a shareable link. Here&amp;rsquo;s what it looks like in action:
You can try it out yourself at http://www.sharemyalbums.me/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A running list of great books I recommend</title>
      <link>https://tonykappen.com/posts/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 18:16:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tonykappen.com/posts/first/</guid>
      <description>Surely you&amp;rsquo;re joking Mr.Feynman by Richard Feynmann
 An autobiography by nobel prize winning physicist Richard Feynmann. This book is very fun to read and feynmann is an easy character to root for. Ultimately this book offered me valuable lessons in not taking yourself too seriously while at the same time pursuing anything with a great deal of integrity.  Thinking fast and slow by Daniel Kahneman
 The main idea of this book is that your mind really consists of two systems:  A fast system that makes decisions quickly based on biases and heuristics (system 1) A slow system that is used when we make decisions after careful deliberation and consideration (system 2)   Kahneman argues that most of our decisions are made with the system 1 part of our minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://tonykappen.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 16:25:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tonykappen.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there!
This is a place where I think about things, and then write them down.
Here is my resume</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>